http://roneyfuneralhome.com/runtime.php?SiteId=288228&NavigatorId=1375154&op=privacy

Search
Use the form above to find your loved one. You can search using the name of your loved one, or any family name for current or past services entrusted to our firm.
Click here to view all obituaries
Search Obituaries
Immediate Need
We are here to help you. If you have need of our services, please call us, day or night, at:
(508) 839-4491
To better prepare yourself, we have provided you with some helpful information regarding the immediate need process.
Contact Us / Location
Roney Funeral Home
152 Worcester Street
PO Box 75
North Grafton, MA 01536
Phone: (508) 839-4491
Fax:
Email: Roneyfuneralhome@gmail.com
Home
Obituaries
About Us
Our Firm
Our Story
Our Facilities
What Makes Us Unique
Burial or Graveside Services
What is a Funeral?
Our Burial Services
How to Plan a Burial Service
Traditional Funeral Services
Frequently Asked Questions
Cremation Services
What is Cremation?
Our Cremation Options
Why Choose Cremation
The Cremation Process
Frequently Asked Questions
Remembrance Services
Memorial Services
What is a Memorial Service?
Why a Memorial Service?
Celebrations-of-Life
Funerals vs. Celebrations of Life
Frequently Asked Questions
Specialty Funeral Services
Veteran Services
Ash Scattering Services
Memorialization Services
Funeral Planning
Order Flowers
Ordering flowers from our site ensures that your order will reach us or the family in a timely manner, and your gesture of support will remain acknowledged in the Book of Memories for future generations. We only work with local florists so we can maintain the sense of urgency and quality of your selections. We thank you for helping to support the family during their time of need, and will fondly remember your kind gesture.
Click Here
Immediate Need
If you have immediate need of our services, we're available for you 24 hours a day.
Pre-Arrangement
A gift to your family, sparing them hard decisions at an emotional time.
Order Flowers
Offer a gift of comfort and beauty to a family suffering from loss.
The Talk of a Lifetime
Sharing stories and reflecting on a person’s life offers opportunities to remember how our loved ones shaped and influenced our lives.
Privacy Policy
Roney Funeral Home Privacy Policy
At Roney Funeral Home, we understand that the
privacy of our visitors and the knowledge of our use of information collected
from each visitor is important in our activities. Please feel free to read our
privacy policy and we encourage you to contact our firm about any of the
information located below if you need further assistance.
Contact Information:
If you feel that there is a need to contact
our firm, please use one of the following methods:
Mail:
Roney Funeral Home152 Worcester StreetPO Box 75North Grafton, MA, USA01536
Phone:
that is used when surfing our web site. We use this information for Site Traffic
Statistics and analysis. We also receive
your IP Address when you complete a search or purchase on our site in order to help our firm
better recognize what is being searched by our visitors. All IP Addresses and
Domain Names are kept with the utmost confidentiality.
Use of Cookies
A cookie is used by Roney Funeral Home only when
there is persistent data that is required to use the Web Site, ie.
Administration Mode, and when an E-Commerce order form is being completed. For
general viewing of pages, there is no use of cookies.
When a user wishes to purchase product(s)
they will be asked to complete an online form.
When a user completes a section of the form and clicks on the "Next" button, not
only does the form progress to the Next page but a cookie is created on the
visitor's computer with the information that they just completed. The purpose of
the shopping basket cookie is to remember your information so that if you leave
or get disconnected and come back to the order form our server will be able to
complete the sections of the order form for you including product
selected.
E-Commerce Module
To ensure that all data remains
private and secure, we exclusively use secure network
connections. These secure network connections are the only way that
credit card and other personal information is handled. Any and all
sensitive authorization data, including but not limited to credit card
information is never stored by Roney Funeral Home, any employee therein or
FrontRunner Professional. All payment details are securely transmitted
by third party processors on secure networks connections. If you have
any questions please
contact accountingdept@frontrunner360.com.
Questions & Comments
If you have questions, comments or concerns
with either the way we use the information that is collected from your web
browser or our privacy policy, please feel free to contact our firm.
North Grafton,
